Do it
[music] I am
polite to you guys in a calibrated manner
because how to calculate dirty bombs it will
not be available near the village,
this is our
Ghagra for everyone
and
if not for anyone then a little bit here and
you can see that this is
1 inch of
this
company
plus one one female child child
child 1 sister is showing that means it is
cream that means the cream is for 130 positive months
2.5 Kun
Kun
subscribe
subscribe here we have to give
you guys
with unity one child
child
ghee here there were two
fifteen years quantity rocket you
can see here if you want to take quality for paan feeding then the
Pakistan columns will be
cooked 16800 arrows that you have to pay you do
n't need to go anywhere
you can check from here if we
want to talk then we will soon here 200
people if it is
serious then I am one then here the
husband's hand will not be forgiven for 22 the hand
is of 128 wife's
Ghagra's wife  Offer prayers in the basket
Voice mail came true Yes, Bell and a child I
want to take a policy in the union of two hearts I will
tell you anything now She has been
kept I assume husband Firoz
675 Alka
Yagnik has
a child
16 thousand 909
2921 A girl customer instead of you 10
laptops are studying so
this 26,000 382
382 is a problem of two
Do it for ₹10 The
biggest company of this year has covered it
But if you do it once and find out then
what should you do Village Yes, this is them that you
cover your children and leave two children
Snowman Bank Part
1 result with two children together
Charts
This is a simple product means college
went to everyone
that I have my mobile You can show it to him that you
can keep it on the mobile It is not necessary
so
how will you get all the details in your phone from here
I had handed it over to you people before coming into such a condition of demanding mark again by the village ho
laugh  So that you never face any problem,
you guys should take as much
care as possible,
then
I have
discussed with as many people as possible, I will have to download it in my mobile,
who has done the
work, tell me your Kharkiya Madhu Sharma
Rakesh Sharma Sharma Sharma
Balveer Singh
ghee madam
means password
village
ghhr k ok ok
now
before showing you the application, let me add something else, let's
put the photo
here, this is our item, in
this way
you will log in to Star 2.0 application in your mobile,
then you get the option that you cannot login,
ok
today after clicking on turn edit footer,
this will totally open in front of you,
that is your agent portal, here
I have entered ID password generator
ID and password here ghee
them, you
should go there
and
subscribe
here enter agent means this is not to be done here
you have to
write
ghhr here,
I am going on my way, let's
login, will enter the cutting here, will
enter the agent examined ID, I will click next here,
I have an OTP here it is
Agarwal Vivek, the
OTP will be visible here if I am not entering the OTP
If you click here
and enter your password, anything can happen, the
mobile application will start, but
this mobile application will work only when you have
received an email from the company, which is an email-centric URL link to the website's email ID.
After clicking on the blue link, you will see the details.
Look here,
submit it here. I don't know
why
I'll take a look at it. If there's a problem, I'll fold it. You
can go to losp.net. It's not like that, I'll run it. I
tried to run it, but it's not working.
[laughs]
Ajay,
so let's see, my application is in front of you. Let's
work
quickly on the application. This is our annual office, which
I mentioned. Let's
log in, so I've made a request. Logging in
means that you have to
come to a meeting, but the purpose of this meeting is to
use the
mobile phone. It
depends on whether you
keep it as quickly as possible, so let's
start it.
Look, there's
no registration requirement here. You just
click on it.
So
we have one that
after that Pooja Total I want to install
touch on the [ __ ], work here
side problem you have to remove mask sexual,
I am taking care of this Kalp and wife,
tell me your problem, I looked at the
Tower Defense
application once more, I just opened it and
nothing happened, if I want to go to dance class then
this option will be available, it is
asking for a PIN like Mike, so I
want, so
I am adding it here, nothing if it
asks for mobile number then I will enter
voice mail ID, if you want then I will enter ABC@gmail.com in the mail ID, let's
click on former cricketer,
it will rotate, the premium will come out in front of you, it is
very simple, it is
scientific, that is why it is very easy to remove love,
after this another application of ours is
SHP Calculator
SHP Tar Help Premium Calculator,
this is also very simple, I
was removing someone's premium, Tulsi is on death,
I will open your juice, see all
our Taj Mahal plants, here
you can see all the plants, the property
owner can complain to me in our daily  Ghr
Ghr
A bit apps
with a comprehensive policy and a half
comprehensive quality you want to meet I have
appointed comprehensive quality I have
clicked on it
whether the company asks behind enter name if you know someone's
name then that's great if you don't know then
why not someone like this you
can also get it by writing ABC or Sir
write your name random here a
cute policy is asking for the term so I want to
quickly take a moment
and click here
you use
WhatsApp in
this way
ghee that uses very good
quality
WhatsApp
click here and from here you
can download it by clicking here
from Ghr
I have many office you should know how to use the application
after this there is our application Agent Office I will
tell you a little about you too many times it happens
that the customer is very professional and
in the serial demands that he
give me a very good PDF so for this you
can use Edit Topics our Agent Office
application this is an application of avatar it
is a simple application scandal date company
's rate chart medium enroll till some  It is available, let's
open it and work on it, we are
giving star comprehensive quality,
here we check the Hukum Principal Individual,
Individual but is at the
top, right now I am telling you
people this is for Gwalior behind the college,
it is optional,
Jai Hind,
God, click on the fifth one here, make a
cut, if you
want this torn one of mine then take it, I have put it on WhatsApp, it is
not primitive, let's do intercourse,
see, in this way Ghaghra,
you can soon send a message in your according
details, it is
on WhatsApp,
you can also use these applications very
well, like the level
more, thank you, my name, insurance
advisor no. contact number, my mail ID is
very good, so you should use it,
if you
click on it, it
means that you have a
very modern professional life,
send it by making tension, so
MP3,
now if I download and open this,
apart from that, madam, show me, then you say
hello hello,
it is absolutely free  China, if
you do more products in this, see,
teachers' benefits of our policy also go,
one and a half companies, then I will send them, we
can help,
pimples plate is exactly like this, any
one mountain pass, then the rule is not, no, instead of sir, it is very
near, then when
we share it, then
also we get nocturnal emission, if you are going to
talk to someone on your mobile, if you are going to have a meeting, you should
not only have a mobile, you should
also have a professional file,
we do ghrelin,
so you should
maintain it very well and give you
whatever you want
in making good piles
and chaat available, how do you do that the
paper that is pasted on the paneer that is pasted on me, you
can put this disgusting plant kilometer in our team in the market,
friends,
I have turned it around
that today I have such a point not only in the office,
I have got calls
at home also, I get calls on
holidays also, I get calls on Sundays also, so
I have to take care of the calls, I have to
tell the premium there also, but if I do
not have the file  I cannot depend on my mobile for 24 hours
that I have these points
at my home Bhosale Palt, if you
ask anyone for premium then I will definitely tell you
that I am crazy,
how will I put it in the 9th PPT file
because there are a lot of points in it,
we will take a printout, we apply tikuli, we
apply oil,
its printout
is
properly and there is a
meeting
or I have told you 23.1 more points,
all these should be maintained which will be helpful to the customer for everything properly,
Magna
problem has happened in
this country, so now from the button of medicine
Meghnad, send a message on that,
when you tell me your question is
not going, is there any gentleman who
means he has just come out of hypertension or means that those who
say
and give
this
that you use family m.a.  But
if
you have robbed their family back please
[Music]
that I am fine
why is he alone
[Music]
for scientific journal name egg fried food quality if there are going to be two people,
three people, four lakh people in the policy I don't need
everyone's name Apple ID
proof
of date of birth to you
torch light
weight this is the time of all of us half inch and waist
if there is any - maybe of a small child from yesterday then we do
not need their hybrid
I ghost's name Kavita date of birth height
weight email id
contact number
my tab rail what does
your patient customer do whatever
seed approximate annual income is
also required we need
nominee's details policy is going to be a loss is there is no
chronic disease of any kind please
confirm with the customer also I will do it
after making the payment so if possible then
definitely take that tweet of Kashmir from the customer that
it is very light if you do
shroud normally on edit footer then
click on any detail  I'll appoint you somewhere to do that.
Now,
tell me about the answer and nomination.
This last application that you showed me
after four powers, when you edit the HTML
exit poll and the
wire health
home
agent, you
can download it from the Play Store.
[Music]
And compare it with the company's retail
companies. Hey, I'm
talking about that because I can use another company's
sadhu custom
and
so we explain a lot to people and send them
this disgusting thing.
Look, this company is
for those people who hate it. The
internal imagination. So, two things still
remain in today's meeting: which
plant to sell out. So, I think it's
about six months. Today
's meeting has become very long. So,
first of all, thank you so much for staying in the meeting. There will be a
lot of Akbar tomorrow. There is
some more
politics to be done in this.
[Music]
If someone dies during this policy,
then what support does the company provide for it?  You do
n't get ghee, you
don't get money from these companies, but whatever money is
spent on medicines in the company, the
company bears that entire money.
Hello hello yes hello hello,
luv
oh madam, mental customer messages like us,
rather
he is not getting all those things, so
after the exchange he said
that he will get Polyplex spoon and
Tubelight spoon, the salt is complete,
so now it will be available at the school store, it is not
available, it is
okay, there is a
meeting,
whatever I have explained, please do not give any nonsense on it,
understand the killers a little, it will be of no use, so tomorrow again
in this meeting, whatever meeting will be there,
I will scold him for you because you will have to do that
meeting with it, ok ok
ok